[
    {
        "front": "いります ❘",
        "back": "need, require",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "しらべます ❘❘",
        "back": "check, investigate",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "なおします ❘",
        "back": "repair, correct",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅりします ❘❘❘",
        "back": "repair (a machine etc)",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "でんわします ❘❘❘",
        "back": "phone",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "ぼく",
        "back": "I (an informal equivalent of わたし used by men)",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "きみ",
        "back": "you (an informal equivalent of あなた used by men)",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "～くん",
        "back": "Mr. (An informal equivalent of ～さん used by men)",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "うん",
        "back": "yes (an informal equivalent of はい)",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "ううん",
        "back": "no (an informal equivalent of いいえ)",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "サラリーマン",
        "back": "salaried worker, office worker",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "ことば",
        "back": "word, language",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "ぶっか",
        "back": "commodity prices, market prices",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "きもの",
        "back": "kimono (traditional Japanese attire)",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "ビザ",
        "back": "visa",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "はじめ",
        "back": "the beginning",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "おわり",
        "back": "the end",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "こっち",
        "back": "informal equivalent of こちら",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "そっち",
        "back": "informal equivalent of そちら",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "あっち",
        "back": "informal equivalent of あちら",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "どっち",
        "back": "informal equivalent of どちら",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "このあいだ",
        "back": "the other day ",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "みんなで",
        "back": "all together",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "～けど",
        "back": "but (an informal equivalent of が)",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "くにへ  かえるの？",
        "back": "Are you going back to your country?",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "どう するの？",
        "back": "What will you do?",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "どうしよかな",
        "back": "What shall I do?",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "よかったら",
        "back": "if you like",
        "chapter": 20
    },
    {
        "front": "いろいろ",
        "back": "various",
        "chapter": 20
    }
]